{
    "subject": "resource/Aster,_Edmonton",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Aster is a future neighbourhood in southeast Edmonton, Alberta, Canada. It was named for the Aster genus of flowering plants of which heath aster and flat-topped white aster are most common in Alberta.Aster is located within The Meadows and is identified as Neighbourhood 5 within The Meadows Area Structure Plan (ASP).",
    "human_readable": "The comment about Aster Edmonton is: Aster is a future neighbourhood in southeast Edmonton, Alberta, Canada. It was named for the Aster genus of flowering plants of which heath aster and flat-topped white aster are most common in Alberta.Aster is located within The Meadows and is identified as Neighbourhood 5 within The Meadows Area Structure Plan (ASP).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.86744225025177,
            "question": "Which type of plants are most common in Alberta and associated with the neighbourhood's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.769828736782074,
            "question": "Where is the Aster neighbourhood located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7210716009140015,
            "question": "What is the official designation for Aster within The Meadows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.701973021030426,
            "question": "What inspired the name of the Aster neighbourhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6989398002624512,
            "question": "What type of plan outlines the development of Aster and other neighbourhoods in The Meadows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6989176273345947,
            "question": "Which province in Canada is home to the Aster neighbourhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.636136531829834,
            "question": "Is Aster a newly developed or established neighbourhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5892267823219299,
            "question": "Are there any notable characteristics or features of the Aster neighbourhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5649186372756958,
            "question": "Within what geographical region is Aster situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5340019464492798,
            "question": "What is the name of the larger community that encompasses Aster?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about Aster Edmonton is: Aster is a future neighbourhood in southeast Edmonton, Alberta, Canada. It was named for the Aster genus of flowering plants of which heath aster and flat-topped white aster are most common in Alberta.Aster is located within The Meadows and is identified as Neighbourhood 5 within The Meadows Area Structure Plan (ASP).",
            "html": "dbpedia_114_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Within what geographical region is Aster situated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_114_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable characteristics or features of the Aster neighbourhood?",
            "html": "dbpedia_114_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Aster a newly developed or established neighbourhood?",
            "html": "dbpedia_114_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_114_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_114_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_114_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_114_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_114_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_114_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_114_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_114_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_114_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_114_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, I will evaluate whether the statement about Aster Edmonton is correct.\n\nHere's the evaluation:\n\n Statement: Aster is a future neighbourhood in southeast Edmonton, Alberta, Canada. It was named for the Aster genus of flowering plants of which heath aster and flat-topped white aster are most common in Alberta.Aster is located within The Meadows and is identified as Neighbourhood 5 within The Meadows Area Structure Plan (ASP).\n\nThe context information provides the following details:\n\n* A document with file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_114/re-ranker-msmarco/93.txt mentions that Aster is a future neighbourhood in southeast Edmonton, Alberta, Canada. It was named for the Aster genus of flowering plants of which heath aster and flat-topped white aster are most common in Alberta.\n* A document with file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_114/re-ranker-msmarco/119.txt mentions that Aster is a future neighbourhood in southeast Edmonton, Alberta, Canada. It was named for the flowering plant genus Aster, of which heath aster and flat-topped white aster are most common in Alberta.\n* The document with file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_114/re-ranker-msmarco/119.txt also mentions that Aster is located within The Meadows area and was originally identified as Neighbourhood 5 within The Meadows Area Structure Plan (ASP).\n\nBased on the above information, I can confirm that the statement about Aster Edmonton is correct. Therefore:\n\n { \"output\": \"yes\" }"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context information supports the comment about Aster Edmonton. It mentions that Aster is a future neighbourhood in southeast Edmonton, Alberta, Canada, and it was named for the Aster genus of flowering plants, with common species being heath aster and flat-topped white aster. Additionally, it specifies its location within The Meadows area and identifies it as Neighbourhood 5 within The Meadows Area Structure Plan (ASP)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}